applicantstack.com 2017-08-14

# Privacy Policy - ApplicantStack

**Effective date:** This document was last updated on July 22, 2009.

## ACKNOWLEDGMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

Racarie Software is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing www.applicantstack.com, you acknowledge and fully understand Racarie Software’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

Racarie Software collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

### Web Server Logs

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

  * Your Internet protocol address.
  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Name of your Internet service provider.
  * Web page you linked to our site from.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

### Use of Cookies

Racarie Software may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. For example, if you personalize a web page, or navigate within a site, a cookie helps the site to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. Hence, this simplifies the process of delivering relevant content and eases site navigation by providing and saving your preferences and login information as well as providing personalized functionality.

Racarie Software reserves the right to share aggregated site statistics with partner companies, but does not allow other companies to place cookies on our website.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

### Personal Information Users

Visitors to www.applicantstack.com can register for an account. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, email, and company. This information is used to establish your account and enable us to provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

If you sign up for a paid account, we may request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary including:

  * To fulfill your service requests for services.
  * To protect ourselves from liability,
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

## USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES

www.applicantstack.com may contain electronic images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow Racarie Software to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. Racarie Software may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. Racarie Software prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

## ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. If you register for an account you will be able to update your personal information from within your account.

## CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

Racarie Software has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the “updated” date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

## CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at support@applicantstack.com or send your comments to:

Racarie Software  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel  
201 Shannon Oaks Circle  
Suite 200  
Cary, NC 27511

Racarie Software will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
